<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<news>
  <item>
    <date>2025-11-18</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh</title>
    <summary>More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.</summary>
    <image/>
    <url>/news/toyota-kirloskar-motor-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>2025-11-18</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh</title>
    <summary>More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.</summary>
    <image/>
    <url>/news/toyota-kirloskar-motor-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>2025-11-18</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh</title>
    <summary>More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.</summary>
    <image/>
    <url>/news/toyota-kirloskar-motor-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>2025-11-18</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh</title>
    <summary>More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.</summary>
    <image/>
    <url>/news/toyota-kirloskar-motor-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>2025-11-18</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh</title>
    <summary>More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.</summary>
    <image/>
    <url>/news/toyota-kirloskar-motor-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>2025-11-18</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh</title>
    <summary>More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.</summary>
    <image/>
    <url>/news/toyota-kirloskar-motor-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
  </item>
  <item>Press Release</item>
  <item>
    <date>November 18 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh</title>
    <summary>Mangalagiri, 18th November 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the handover of essential classroom infrastructure and learning support materials to rural schools in Andhra Pradesh, under its Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) program for FY 2025-26. As part of this initiative, TKM extended support to 13 government schools in Mangalagiri taluk of Guntur district, benefiting more than 3,600 students.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/nov-18/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>November 14 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Inaugurates New Dealership in Nagaon, Assam </title>
    <summary>Nagaon, 14th November 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the inauguration of its new dealership, Gargya Toyota, in Nagaon, Assam, marking another milestone in the company’s ongoing efforts to strengthen its commitment towards enhancing accessibility, building customer trust, and supporting the growing demand for mobility solutions in the region. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/nov-15/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-inaugurates-new-dealership-in-nagaon-assam.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>November 14 2025</date>
    <title> Toyota Kirloskar Motor Enhances Quality of Education by Upgrading Infrastructure in Government Schools, Chhatrapati Sambhajinagar</title>
    <summary>14th November 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM), on the occasion of Children’s Day, strengthened its commitment to nurture future generations through education. The company has announced the handover of essential school infrastructure and learning support materials to 11 government schools in Chhatrapati Sambhajinagar, Maharashtra, as part of its Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) focus on education.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/nov-14/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-enhances-quality-of-education-by-upgrading-infrastructure-in-government-schools-chhatrapati-sambhajinagar.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>November 11 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor and DRUM TAO Unite for a Spectacular India Tour 2025</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 11th November 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor, in collaboration with Japan’s globally acclaimed performance group, DRUM TAO, today announced the official schedule for the DRUM TAO India Tour 2025. This collaboration symbolizes a fusion of artistic excellence and cross-cultural connection, bringing together two nations that share a deep respect for tradition, innovation, and creativity.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/nov-11/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-and-drum-tao-unite-for-a-spectacular-india-tour-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>November 10 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Wins Two Kaushalya Karnataka Awards at Bengaluru Skill Summit 2025</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 10th November 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has been conferred with two prestigious awards at the Bengaluru Skill Summit 2025, recognizing the company’s outstanding contributions to skill development and human capital building in India.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/nov-10/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-wins-two-kaushalya-karnataka-awards-at-bengaluru-skill-summit-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>November 03 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Strengthens Healthcare Infrastructure in Uttarakhand </title>
    <summary>November 03rd 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has successfully installed medical and non-medical equipment at three health centers in the Khatima Block of Udham Singh Nagar district, Uttarakhand. As part of its FY 2025–26 CSR focus on health &amp; hygiene, TKM has equipped the Sub District Hospital in Khatima and Primary Health Centres in Deori and Chakarpur, collectively benefiting 3,00,000 community members.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/nov-03/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-strengthens-healthcare-infrastructure-in-uttarakhand.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>November 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Sells 42,892 Units in October 2025</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru,01st November 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced its sales results for the festive month of October 2025 as follows:</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-sells-42892-units-in-october-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 31 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Sends 100 Skilled Youth for Global Training to Japan</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 31st October 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced that 100 members will travel to Japan to participate in the Global Skill-Up Training (GST) program at Toyota Motor Corporation. The initiative reflects TKM’s deep commitment to nurturing globally competitive talent and aligns with the Government of India’s Skill India Mission and the Technical Intern Training Program (TITP) — a collaborative framework between the Governments of India and Japan for international skill development and talent exchange.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/oct-31/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-sends-100-skilled-youth-for-global-training-to-japan.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 16 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Launches the Urban Cruiser Hyryder Aero Edition with Exclusive Styling Package</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 16th October 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today unveiled the Urban Cruiser Hyryder Aero Edition, a Limited-Edition styling package that brings an added dimension of prestige and premium appeal to Toyota’s popular SUV. Designed to elevate Hyryder’s on road presence, the Aero Edition blends bold aesthetics with refined detailing to meet the aspirations of customers who seek sophistication, individuality, and modern comfort.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/oct-16/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-launches-the-urban-cruiser-hyryder-aero-edition-with-exclusive-styling-package.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 15 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Expands Pre-Owned Car Network with New Toyota Mobility Solutions Outlet in Chandigarh</title>
    <summary>Chandigarh, 15th October 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the expansion of its dedicated pre-owned car business with the launch of Toyota Mobility Solutions and Services India Pvt. Ltd. (TMSS) operations in Chandigarh. TMSS, a wholly owned subsidiary of TKM, has been established to redefine India’s used car ecosystem by offering transparency, reliability, and excellence aligned with Toyota’s global standards. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/oct-15/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-expands-pre-owned-car-network-with-new-toyota-mobility-solutions-outlet-in-chandigarh.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 13 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Concludes 34th iCARE Initiative, Empowering Rural Women Entrepreneurs Through Self-Help Groups</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 13th October 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the successful completion of its 34th iCARE activity under its Employee Volunteerism Program – iCARE (i, Community Action to Reach Everyone), marking another significant milestone in its journey of social impact. Aligned with TKM’s core DNA of continuous improvement (Kaizen), respect for people, and commitment to sustainability, this initiative reflects the company’s enduring focus on empowering communities and fostering inclusive growth through innovative and eco-conscious solutions. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/oct-13/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-concludes-34th-icare-initiative-empowering-rural-women-entrepreneurs-through-self-help-groups.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 10 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Partners with Government of Karnataka to Strengthen Vocational Education in Automobile Sector</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 10th October 2025:  Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the signing of a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Samagra Shikshana Karnataka (Department of School Education and Literacy), Government of Karnataka, to promote and strengthen vocational education for students studying in Grades 9 to 12.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/oct-10/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-partners-with-government-of-karnataka-to-strengthen-vocational-education-in-automobile-sector.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 09 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Unveils its Sustainability Report 2025</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 09th October 2025 - Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has announced the release of its comprehensive Sustainability Report 2025, reinforcing its commitment to environmental stewardship and sustainable mobility solutions tailored for India's unique developmental landscape. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/oct-09/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-unveils-its-sustainability-report-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 08 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Launches the 2025 Fortuner Leader Edition </title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 08th October 2025: Building on the success of the 2024 LEADER EDITION, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) is set to make an even bolder impression with the launch of 2025 Fortuner LEADER EDITION. With refreshed styling and premium enhancements, this latest edition further amplifies the Fortuner’s commanding road presence, offering customers a sportier and more dynamic appeal.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/oct-08/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-launches-the-2025-fortuner-leader-edition.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 07 2025</date>
    <title>Hon’ble Prime Minister of India Felicitates Toyota Kaushalya Trainee as National Topper in DGT Examination 2024</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 07th October 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) is proud to share that Mr. Manjunatha S, a trainee from Toyota Kaushalya (Flexi MoU Scheme), has been conferred as the National Topper in the All India Trade Test conducted in October 2024 by the Directorate General of Training (DGT) under the Craftsman Training Scheme (CTS). The prestigious honour was presented by the Hon’ble Prime Minister of India, Shri Narendra Modi, during the Kaushal Dikshant Samaroh held on October 4, 2025, in New Delhi.  Mr. Manjunath is the only candidate from Karnataka to receive this distinction at the national level, showcasing exceptional skill, dedication, and professionalism.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/oct-07/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/honble-prime-minister-of-india-felicitates-toyota-kaushalya-trainee-as-national-topper-in-dgt-examination-2024.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>October 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Sells 31,091 units in September 2025</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 01st October 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced its sales results for September 2025 as follows:</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-sells-31091-units-in-september-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 29 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Lays Foundation for Life Skills Training Centre for Bharat Scouts &amp; Guides</title>
    <summary>Chikmagalur, Karnataka, 29th September 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to community development through education, skill enhancement, and youth-focused initiatives, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) announced the groundbreaking of the Bharat Scouts &amp; Guides (BSG) Training and Camping Centre in Chikmagalur district of Karnataka.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/sep-29/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-lays-foundation-for-life-skills-training-centre-for-bharat-scouts-guides.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 25 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Reiterates its Commitment to Sustainability, Marking the World Environment Health Day 2025</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 25th September 2025: Marking World Environment Health Day, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today reaffirmed its long-standing commitment to advancing environmental sustainability and social well-being in India. Guided by the global Toyota Environmental Challenge 2050 (TEC 2050) consisting of six challenges, announced in 2015, TKM continues to reduce its carbon footprint accelerating the transition by going beyond products, embedding sustainable practices in manufacturing operations and across their entire value chain. Further, such eco efforts include conserving natural resources, and enriching communities through impactful projects. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/sep-25/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-reiterates-its-commitment-to-sustainability-marking-the-world-environment-health-day-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 24 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Signs MoU with Government of Uttarakhand to Implement Holistic CSR Initiatives </title>
    <summary>Dehradun, 24th September 2025: Reinforcing its focus on holistic community development, sustainable growth, and social accountability, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has signed an MoU with the Government of Uttarakhand. The MoU covers a wide range of CSR initiatives to be implemented across the state from FY 2025–26 onwards, focusing on key pillars such as education, health &amp; hygiene, environmental sustainability and community development.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/sep-24/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-signs-mou-with-government-of-uttarakhand-to-implement-holistic-csr-initiatives.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 23 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Announces “DRUM TAO” as Brand Ambassadors</title>
    <summary>Bangalore,23rd September 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) proudly announces its association with Japan’s internationally acclaimed performance group, DRUM TAO, as brand ambassadors. Celebrated worldwide for their electrifying performances, intricate choreography, and innovative stagecraft, DRUM TAO will bring a unique musical journey to India through this collaboration.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-drum-tao-as-brand-ambassadors.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 22 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Elevates Safety with 6 Airbags Standard Across All Variants of the Rumion</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 22nd September 2025: In line with its deep-rooted safety philosophy and customer-first approach, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) announced a significant enhancement to its acclaimed family mover, the Toyota Rumion. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/sep-22/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-elevates-safety-with-6-airbags-standard-across-all-variants-of-the-rumion.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 10 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Announces Navratri Offer: Up to ₹1 Lakh Benefits Alongside GST Relief</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 10th September 2025: In pursuit of adding to the joy of the festive season, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) announced a double bonanza for customers. After passing on the complete benefits of the recent GST rate reduction on cars and SUVs, TKM is further enhancing the joy of Navratri with its special campaign – “Buy Now and Pay in 2026” for its customers in the western region. The combined benefits of the GST rate reduction and Toyota’s festive offer make it the perfect time for customers to bring home their favourite Toyota vehicles such as Urban Cruiser Hyryder, Glanza or Urban Cruiser Taisor.  </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/sep-10/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-navratri-offer-up-to-one-lakh-benefits-alongside-gst-relief.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 06 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Announces Price Reductions, Passing on Full Benefits of GST Rate Reduction</title>
    <summary>Bangalore 06th September 2025: In line with its unwavering commitment to customer first philosophy and delivering delightful experiences at every touchpoint, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced that it will fully pass on the benefits of the recent GST rate reduction to its customers. The revised prices will come into effect from 22nd September 2025.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-price-reductions-passing-on-full-benefits-of-gst-rate-reduction.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 03 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Signs MoU with Presidency University, Bengaluru to Launch M. Tech Program in Automotive Information Technology </title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 03rd September 2025: In a significant step towards promoting skill development and educational excellence, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Presidency University (PU), Bengaluru. The agreement aims to introduce a pioneering M. Tech Program in Automotive Information Technology (IT), designed to nurture industry-ready engineers capable of driving innovations in the era of software-defined vehicles and next-gen mobility solutions.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/sep-03/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-signs-mou-with-presidency-university-bengaluru-to-launch-m-tech-program-in-automotive-information-technology.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>September 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Sells 34,236 units in August 2025</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 01st September 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today declared its sales performance as follows:</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-sells-34236-units-in-august-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 18 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Launches Camry Hybrid Electric Vehicle – Sprint Edition</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 18th August 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor Pvt. Ltd. (TKM) today launched the Camry Hybrid Electric Vehicle – Sprint Edition, a sportier and more dynamic expression of its iconic luxury hybrid electric sedan. Featuring a striking dual-tone exterior, matte black enhancements, and an exclusive sports kit*, this new variant blends dynamic aesthetics with refined performance. The Camry Sprint Edition reflects an enthusiastic persona – designed for those who seek fun-to-drive experience wrapped in sporty sophistication.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/aug-18/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-launches-camry-hybrid-electric-vehicle-sprint-edition.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 14 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor unveils exclusive “Drive the Nation” campaign for Government employees across North India</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 14th August 2025: Reaffirming its commitment to customer delight, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has introduced a special campaign, ‘Drive the Nation’, for central and state government employees in North India. Commemorating Independence Day the offer is applicable on Toyota Urban Cruiser Hyryder Model through the month of August.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/aug-14/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-unveils-exclusive-drive-the-nation-campaign-for-government-employees-across-north-india.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 12 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Urban Cruiser Taisor Now Available in Bold New Bluish Black Colour with Enhanced Safety Standardized Across All Variants</title>
    <summary>National, 12th August 2025: In line with its customer-first philosophy and focus on delivering ever-better cars, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced two key enhancements to its popular compact SUV, the Urban Cruiser Taisor — the introduction of new Bluish Black exterior colour and the standardization of six airbags across all variants.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/aug-12/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/toyota-urban-cruiser-taisor-now-available-in-bold-new-bluish-black-colour-with-enhanced-safety-standardized-across-all-variants.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 08 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens Commitment to Sustainable and Inclusive Growth Through Holistic CSR Initiatives</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 08th August 2025: On Tuesday the 5th of August 2025, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) unveiled its CSR Report for FY 2024–25, outlining the company’s sustained and strategic efforts towards empowering communities and advancing national development goals. The report was formally released by Mr. Suresh Heblikar, Environmentalist and Filmmaker, in the presence of Mr. Ramesh Rao, Vice President, External Affairs &amp; CSR, Toyota Kirloskar Motor and other senior executives from the Company.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/aug-08/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-deepens-commitment-to-sustainable-and-inclusive-growth-through-holistic-csr-initiatives.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 07 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Mobility Foundation Announces Finalists for $3 Million Global Challenge To Transform Crowd Management&#xD;
        in Varanasi’s Old City</title>
    <summary>VARANASI, INDIA (August 07 2025) — The Toyota Mobility Foundation (TMF) today announced five finalists for the $3 million Sustainable Cities Challenge, focused on transforming crowd management solutions in Varanasi’s historic city, Kashi. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/aug-07/thumb-02-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/toyota-mobility-foundation-announces-finalists-for-3-million-global-challenge-to-transform-crowd-management-in-varanasi-old-city.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 07 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Signs Renewal Agreement with Kamarajar Port </title>
    <summary>National, August 07th 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to Make-in-India and aimed at further strengthening India’s role as a strategic automotive manufacturing hub, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has renewed its Wharfage Rate Agreement with Kamarajar Port Limited (KPL).</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/aug-07/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-signs-renewal-agreement-with-kamarajar-port.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 06 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Technical Training Institute Marks the Convocation for its 16th Batch of Students</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 06th August 2025: Toyota Technical Training Institute (TTTI) today celebrated the convocation of its 16th batch of students, marking another significant milestone in its mission to skill and empower rural youth through world-class training in advanced manufacturing practices. A total of 200 students—comprising 60 Regular TTTI students and 140 Toyota Kaushalya course students from rural Karnataka—were honoured during the ceremony for successfully completing their holistic development journey across Knowledge, Skill, Body, and Attitude.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/aug-06/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/toyota-technical-training-institute-marks-the-convocation-for-its-16th-batch-of-students.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 05 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Innova Completes 20 Glorious Years in India, Trusted by 12 Lakh Plus Customers</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 05th August 2025: Marking a proud milestone in its journey in India, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today celebrated 20 remarkable years of the Toyota Innova, a name that has grown to become a trusted companion for millions of Indian families and businesses. With over 12 lakh plus units sold across its three offerings, Innova, Innova Crysta, and Innova HyCross, the brand stands as a symbol of unwavering customer trust and lasting value. Over the past two decades, the Innova has continuously evolved to reflect the changing aspirations of the customers in India, while staying rooted in Toyota’s core philosophy of Quality, Durability, and Reliability (QDR). This is not just a milestone of numbers, but a celebration of innumerable journeys, memories, and moments made possible by Innova that has truly stood the test of time.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/aug-05/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/toyota-innova-completes-20-glorious-years-in-india-trusted-by-12-lakh-plus-customers.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>August 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Sells 32,575 units in July 2025</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 01 August 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced its sales performance as follows:</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-sells-32575-units-in-july-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 30 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Signs MoU with Government of Maharashtra to Develop Government School Infrastructure at Bidkin </title>
    <summary>Bidkin, Maharashtra, 30th July 2025: In line with its enduring commitment to sustainable social impact and holistic community development, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Zilla Parishad to support the comprehensive infrastructure development of Zilla Parishad Kendriya Prathamik School (ZPKPS) in Bidkin, Chhatrapati Sambhaji Nagar.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jul-30/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-signs-mou-with-government-of-maharashtra-to-develop-government-school-infrastructure-at-bidkin.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 15 2025</date>
    <title>Government of Karnataka Recognizes WorldSkills 2024 Winners from Toyota Kirloskar Motor </title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 15th July 2025: Reaffirming its commitment to the “Skill India Mission” and India’s aspiration for “Viksit Bharat 2047,” Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today proudly announced the felicitation of their ten talented employees by the Government of Karnataka for their exceptional achievements at the WorldSkills Competition 2024 held in Lyon, France.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jul-15/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/government-of-karnataka-recognizes-worldskills-2024-winners-from-tkm.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 11 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor announces Six airbag as a standard and a New Accessory package “Prestige edition” in Glanza</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 11th July 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced two significant updates to its hatchback, the Toyota Glanza, aimed at further strengthening safety and enhancing overall customer value.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jul-11/thumb-2-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-six-airbag-as-a-standard-and-a-new-accessory-package-prestige-edition-in-glanza.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 11 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Expands its Presence in Northeast India with the Launch of a New Dealership in Guwahati, Assam</title>
    <summary>Guwahati, 11th July 2025: In a significant step towards strengthening its presence in India’s Northeast region, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today inaugurated a new dealership – Gargya Toyota, in the historic city of Guwahati, Assam. The new facility underscores Toyota’s continued focus on enhancing accessibility, fostering customer trust, and supporting the growing demand for mobility solutions in emerging regional markets.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jul-11/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-expands-its-presence-in-northeast-india-with-the-launch-of-a-new-dealership-in-guwahati-assam.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 07 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Unveils Exclusive ‘Prestige Package’ for the Urban Cruiser Hyryder</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 07th July 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to enhancing customer delight, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has introduced a limited-period ‘Prestige Package’ for its popular self-charging hybrid SUV—the Urban Cruiser Hyryder. Thoughtfully designed to elevate the SUV’s already bold and sophisticated appeal, this exclusive accessory bundle offers customers an added layer of style, presence, and functionality for everyday driving.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jul-07/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-unveils-exclusive-prestige-package-for-the-urban-cruiser-hyryder.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 04 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor inaugurates New City Office in Chhatrapati Sambhaji Nagar</title>
    <summary>Chhatrapati Sambhaji Nagar, 04 July 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the inauguration of its new city office in Chhatrapati Sambhaji Nagar (CSN), Maharashtra — a key milestone towards strengthening its presence in the State of Maharashtra and reaffirming its commitment to contributing India’s automotive industry.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jul-04/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-inaugurates-new-city-office-in-chhatrapati-sambhaji-nagar.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 03 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Announces, “Awesome Toyota Service Campaign” across all its Dealerships in South India</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 03rd July 2025: Get Monsoon-Ready with Exciting Offers on Service, Tyres, Accessories &amp; More! Toyota is bringing a splash of care and value this season with the launch of its ‘Awesome Toyota Service Campaign’ — an initiative across all authorized Toyota dealerships in Southern Part of India. Whether it’s preparing your vehicle for the rains, refreshing interiors with monsoon care, or ensuring a smooth ride with tyre and battery checks, this campaign is all about keeping you safe, comfortable, and road-ready this monsoon!</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jul-03/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-awesome-toyota-service-campaign-across-all-its-dealerships-in-south-india.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 02 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Innova HyCross Secures 5-Star Safety Rating Under Bharat NCAP</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 02nd July 2025: In a significant testament to Toyota Kirloskar Motor’s (TKM) uncompromised commitment to safety, the much-appreciated Innova HyCross has been awarded a 5-star safety rating under the Bharat New Car Assessment Programme (Bharat NCAP) — India’s most comprehensive vehicle safety evaluation framework. This milestone marks the company’s unwavering and inherent focus on delivering ever-safer mobility solutions to its valued customers. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jul-02/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/toyota-innova-hycross-secures-5-star-safety-rating-under-bharat-ncap.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>July 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Sales up 5% in June 2025, first-half 2025 numbers grow by 16%</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 01st July 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced its sales performance as follows: </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-sales-up-5-in-june-2025-first-half-2025-numbers-grow-by-16.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>June 27 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Culminates Environment Month 2025 </title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 27th June 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to environmental stewardship across the value chain, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today marked the successful culmination of Environment Month 2025, under the theme ‘Sustainable Resource Management Drive’ through ‘Zero-Base Thinking’ including plastic elimination efforts.  This year’s edition featured a series of impactful initiatives aimed at embedding sustainability into every facet of the organisation – from green logistics to promoting resource-conscious behaviour and driving community sensitization on environment protection. Engaging over 3,100 participants, the initiative united employees, partners (suppliers, dealers) and community members in collective commitment to sustainable practices – both within the workplace and across the broader community. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jun-27/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-culminates-environment-month-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>June 25 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Exchanges Memorandum of Understanding with Ohmium to advance Scalable Hydrogen-Based Energy Solutions in India</title>
    <summary>Delhi, 25th June 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to Carbon Neutrality and clean energy innovation, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today exchanged a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Bengaluru-based Ohmium International, a leading PEM hydrogen technology provider, to co-develop Green Hydrogen-based integrated power solutions in India. This strategic undertaking highlights Toyota’s pivotal role in fuel cell technology and advancing Green Hydrogen as the clean fuel of the future. It highlights the company’s relentless efforts to foster a robust Hydrogen economy across mobility and stationary applications. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jun-26/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-exchanges-memorandum-of-understanding-with-ohmium-to-advance-scalable-hydrogen-based-energy-solutions-in-india.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>June 12 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Announces Special Early-Festive Offer Packed with Exciting Customer Benefits</title>
    <summary>Delhi, 12th June 2025: Adding festive cheer early to the car buying journey, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has announced an exciting limited-period campaign — ‘Buy Now, Pay in Navratri’, applicable on its popular models, the Toyota Glanza and Urban Cruiser Hyryder. This specially curated scheme is designed in association with Toyota Financial Services (TFS) to offer customers unmatched flexibility and convenience in car ownership.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jun-12/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-special-early-festive-offer-packed-with-exciting-customer-benefits.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>June 05 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Flags Off Environment Month 2025 - Themed “Sustainable Resource Management Drive”</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 05th June 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today flagged off the Environment Month 2025, reaffirming its commitment to sustainability through the theme “Sustainable Resource Management Drive”. This initiative aligns with the broader goals of the Toyota Environmental Challenge 2050 and the global theme of “Enhancing Awareness Towards Realising Toyota Global Vision 2050”. The campaign aims to strengthen a culture of sustainability across the company and its value chain. A key element of this year’s focus is the adoption of ‘Zero-Base Thinking’ – a strategy that involves reevaluating all resources from the ground up and retaining only those that contribute genuine value, thereby promoting long-term sustainable efficiency through Refuse, Recycle (circular economy), Reuse and Reduce (4Rs).</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jun-05/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-flags-off-environment-month-2025-themed-sustainable-resource-management-drive.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>June 02 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Launches Fortuner and Legender Neo Drive 48V Variants</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 02nd June 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the introduction of the Fortuner and Legender in a new Neo Drive avatar/grade. Equipped with an advanced 48Volt system, the new Neo Drive Variants offer improved fuel efficiency, enhanced driving performance, and greater comfort—delivering a more refined experience in urban settings and off-road conditions.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jun-02/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-launches-fortuner-and-legender-neo-drive-48v-variants.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>June 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Sustains Positive Sales Momentum in May 2025</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 01st June 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) continues to uphold its sales momentum, registering a growth of 22% over the same period last year. The company sold 30,864 units during the month, including 29,280 units in domestic sales and 1,584 units exported. In May 2024, TKM had sold 25,273 units.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-sustains-positive-sales-momentum-in-may-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 26 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Fortuner and Legender Achieve Landmark Milestone of 3-Lakh Sales in India</title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 26th May 2025: Reinforcing its dominant presence in India’s premium SUV market, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced a significant milestone—cumulative sales of 3-lakh units of the Fortuner and Legender. This achievement underscores not only the unmatched popularity of these premium SUVs but also Toyota’s commitment to delivering reliable and high-performance that perfectly blend power with precision.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/may-26/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/toyota-fortuner-and-legender-achieve-landmark-milestone-of-3-lakh-sales-in-india.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 21 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Expands its Presence in Northeast India with the Launch of a New Dealership in Jorhat, Assam</title>
    <summary>Assam, 21st May 2025: In a significant step towards strengthening its presence in India’s Northeast region, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today inaugurated a new dealership – Preet Toyota, in the historic city of Jorhat, Assam. The new facility underscores Toyota’s continued focus on enhancing accessibility, fostering customer trust, and supporting the growing demand for mobility solutions in emerging regional markets.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/may-21/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-expands-its-presence-in-northeast-india-with-the-launch-of-a-new-dealership-in-jorhat-assam.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 19 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Announces, ‘Mega Summer Celebration’ </title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 19th May 2025: Exciting Offers across Sales, Service, Used Cars, Accessories &amp; More! Toyota is turning up the heat this season with the launch of its ‘Mega Summer Celebration’ — an event across all authorized Toyota dealerships in Southern Part of India. Be it a plan to buy a new car, servicing existing cars, explore certified used cars, or upgrade the vehicle accessories, it is the customer’s moment to steal the deal!</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/may-19/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-mega-summer-celebration-bengaluru.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 17 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Showcases the Hilux Black Edition at Amana Toyota, Palakkad in the State of Kerala</title>
    <summary>Palakkad, 17th May 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) showcased the Hilux Black Edition at its dealership — Amana Toyota, located at Poriyani (Mundur), Palakkad, Kerala. With its bold design, advanced technology, and unmatched reliability, the Hilux Black Edition is designed for those who seek both adventure and everyday practicality. Built to conquer challenging terrains and city roads alike, this special edition embodies Toyota’s legendary toughness while offering a lifestyle statement tailored to the aspirations of customers in this region and beyond. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/may-17/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-showcases-the-hilux-black-edition-at-amana-toyota-palakkad-in-the-state-of-kerala.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 15 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Announces, ‘Mega Summer Celebration’ </title>
    <summary>Delhi, 15th May 2025: Exciting Offers across Sales, Service, Used Cars, Accessories &amp; More! Toyota is turning up the heat this season with the launch of its ‘Mega Summer Celebration’ — an initiative across all authorized Toyota dealerships in Northern Part of India. Be it a plan to buy a new car, servicing existing cars, explore certified used cars, or upgrade the vehicle accessories, it is the customer’s moment to steal the deal!</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/may-15/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-mega-summer-celebration.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 14 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Technical Training Institute (TTTI) Opens Admissions for Batch of 2025-2028</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 14th May 2025: In line with its commitment to skill development and community empowerment, Toyota Technical Training Institute (TTTI) today announced the commencement of the admission process for 2025-2028 batch of the TTTI Regular Program. This pioneering initiative aims to transform academically inclined youth from economically challenged backgrounds in Karnataka into globally competitive technicians through industry-relevant training, fully sponsored by Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM).</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/may-14/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/toyota-technical-training-institute-ttti-opens-admissions-for-batch-of-2025-2028.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 07 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Showcases Iconic Hilux Black Edition at Topsel Toyota, Siliguri </title>
    <summary>Siliguri, 07th May 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) showcased the Hilux Black Edition at its dealership - Topsel Toyota, Siliguri, West Bengal. With its bold design, advanced technology, and unmatched reliability, the Hilux Black Edition is designed for those who seek both adventure and everyday practicality. Built to conquer challenging terrains and city roads alike, this special edition embodies Toyota’s legendary toughness while offering a lifestyle statement tailored to the aspirations of customers in this region and beyond. This event underscores Toyota’s continued commitment to expanding its footprint and product offerings in the North-East, a region of growing strategic importance.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/may-07/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-showcases-iconic-hilux-black-edition-at-topsel-toyota-siliguri.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 02 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Introduces Exclusive Edition of Innova HyCross with Elegant Design and 19 Premium Features</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 02nd May 2025: Staying true to its customer-first philosophy, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the launch of the Exclusive Edition of the Innova HyCross available in the ZX(O) grade. Building upon the remarkable success of the Innova HyCross, this new rendition offers distinguished styling and enhanced cabin experience with the below offerings:</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/may-02/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-introduces-exclusive-edition-of-innova-hycross-with-elegant-design-and-19-premium-features.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>May 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Sells 27,324 units in the month of April 2025</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 01st May 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) recorded a growth of 33% in April 2025 over the same period last year, selling 27,324 units. In April 2025, domestic sales stood at 24,833 units, while exports contributed 2,491 units. In April 2024, TKM had sold 20,494 units.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-sells-27324-units-in-the-month-of-april-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 29 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Reaffirms Long-Term Commitment to Road Safety Across India</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 29th April 2025: In alignment with its vision of building a safer and more responsible mobility ecosystem, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) reiterates its long-standing commitment to advancing road safety through structured initiatives across the country. TKM’s efforts span awareness, education, and innovation, positively impacting over 10 lakh individuals through its comprehensive road safety programs.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-29/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-reaffirms-long-term-commitment-to-road-safety-across-india.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 25 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Concludes Skill Festival 2025, Reinforces Commitment to Building India’s Skilled Workforce</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 25th April 2025: Reaffirming its long-standing commitment to shaping the future of India’s skilled workforce, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today successfully concluded its much-anticipated Skill Festival 2025, held at its Bidadi facility, celebrating the spirit of vocational excellence, innovation, and youth empowerment. The event marked the culmination of months of intensive skill development programs and contests aimed at nurturing India’s future-ready talent pool.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-25/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-concludes-skill-festival-2025-reinforces-commitment-to-building-indias-skilled-workforce.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 24 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor and Camdir Toyota in association with Govt. of Arunachal Pradesh established 68th Toyota Technical Education Program (T-TEP) and STAR Scholarship Program at Government ITI, Roing to empower youth with automotive skills</title>
    <summary>Roing, 24th April 2025: Continuing its commitment to the nation’s ‘Skill India’ and ‘Make in India’ missions Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) in collaboration with the Skill Development &amp; Entrepreneurship department instituted its 68th Toyota Technical Education Program (T-TEP) and the “Scholarship program for Technical Education and Recognition” [STAR] initiative under T-TEP at Industrial Training Institute (ITI), Roing, Arunachal Pradesh. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-24/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-and-camdir-toyota-in-association-with-govt-of-arunachal-pradesh.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 21 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Exchanges MoU with Government of Mizoram to Drive Holistic Community Development</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 21st April 2025: In a significant step towards fostering holistic growth and sustainable development in the Northeast, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has exchanged a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Government of Mizoram. Held in Aizawl, the MoU exchange ceremony marks an important milestone in TKM’s efforts to contribute meaningfully to the region’s progress through focused, community-centric CSR initiatives. Under this collaboration.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-21/thumb-1-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-exchanges-mou-with-government-of-mizoram-to-drive-holistic-community-development.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 21 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Reaffirms its Commitment to Environmental Sustainability on ‘Earth Day’</title>
    <summary>This ‘Earth Day’, as the world unites under the theme ‘Our Power, Our Planet’, we are reminded that the responsibility to safeguard our environment lies with each one of us. At Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM), this commitment is embedded in our core values – driving us not only to innovate and introduce varied electrified vehicle technologies (xEVs*) including alternate fuel driven powertrains, through a multiple pathway approach, but also lead collective sustainable initiatives including adoption of renewable energy in pursuit of an environmentally resilient world. In alignment with the global Toyota’s Environmental Challenge 2050 (Challenge 1-6), announced in 2015, we at TKM are accelerating our transition toward carbon neutrality, by going beyond products, embedding sustainable practices in manufacturing operations and across our entire value chain.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-21/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-reaffirms-its-commitment-to-environmental-sustainability-on-earth-day.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 17 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Enhances Education and Healthcare Infrastructure in Raichur under its CSR Program</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 17th April 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to quality education and holistic community development, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has taken a significant step to empower communities in Raichur district, Karnataka. As part of its Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) program, TKM has extended vital educational and healthcare infrastructure support to address persistent developmental challenges in Raichur, an Aspirational District identified by NITI Aayog.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-17/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-enhances-education-and-healthcare-infrastructure-in-raichur-under-its-csr-program.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 16 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Expands Footprint in Western India with Launch of the New Facility of DJ Toyota in Ahmedabad</title>
    <summary>Ahmedabad, 16th April 2025: In line with its vision to enhance customer reach and deliver best-in-class ownership experiences, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today inaugurated its latest state-of-the-art facility — DJ Toyota in Ahmedabad, Gujarat. This marks Toyota’s 7th customer touchpoint in the city, and the 1157th in the country.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-16/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-expands-footprint-in-western-india-with-launch-of-the-new-facility-of-dj-toyota-in-ahmedabad.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 11 2025</date>
    <title>New Initiative Uses Behavioural Science to Encourage Bengaluru Metro Adoption </title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 11th April 2025: The Bengaluru Metro Rail Corporation Limited (BMRCL), Bengaluru Metropolitan Transport Corporation (BMTC), and the Electronics City Industries Association (ELCIA), in collaboration with Toyota Mobility Foundation (TMF) and WRI India today launched the “STAMP: Nudging Commuter Behaviour” — a pioneering initiative that leverages behavioural science and technology to encourage commuters to shift from personal vehicles to public transport.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-11/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/new-initiative-uses-behavioural-science-to-encourage-bengaluru-metro-adoption.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 07 2025</date>
    <title>Urban Cruiser Hyryder Elevates Mobility Experience with Advanced Feature Enhancements</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 07th April 2025:  Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced that it has introduced feature upgrades in the Urban Cruiser Hyryder that redefine safety, comfort, and convenience. The latest enhancements underscores Toyota’s commitment to customer-centric innovation, seamlessly incorporating valuable feedback and evolving market trends to elevate the driving experience.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/apr-07/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/urban-cruiser-hyryder-elevates-mobility-experience-with-advanced-feature-enhancements.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>April 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Records Best-Ever Fiscal Performance in FY24-25 with 28% Growth </title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 01st April 2025:  Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced its highest-ever sales in a financial year, marking a key milestone in the company’s growth journey in India. For FY24-25, TKM sold 3,37,148 units, recording a double-digit growth of 28% compared to 2,63,512 units sold in FY23-24. This achievement reaffirms the success of TKM’s long-term vision, built on a customer-first philosophy and a versatile product lineup. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-records-best-ever-fiscal-performance-in-fy24-25-with-28-growth.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>March 24 2025</date>
    <title>Bidadi Industries Association Foundation Hosts 2nd Edition of Toyota Bidadi Half Marathon, Championing Fitness, Road Safety &amp; Sustainability</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 24th March 2025: The Bidadi Industries Association Foundation (BIAF) successfully hosted the 2nd edition of the Toyota Bidadi Half Marathon on 23rd March 2025 at Jollywood Studios, nestled in the scenic Bidadi Industrial Area on the outskirts of Bengaluru. Centred around the theme “Run for Safety &amp; Sustainability,” witnessed a turnout of over 4,500 registered participants from diverse walks of life—highlighting a rising passion for fitness, road safety awareness, and environmental responsibility. Toyota Kirloskar Motor, given its strong commitment to road safety and sustainability, proudly supported the event as the Title Sponsor.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/mar-24/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/bidadi-industries-association-foundation-hosts-edition-of-toyota-bidadi-half-marathon-championing-fitness-road-safety-sustainability.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>March 20 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Reaffirms its Commitment to Environmental Stewardship and Sustainable Practices on the World Forest Day and World Water Day 2025</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 20th March 2025: As the world marks ‘World Forest Day’ and ‘World Water Day’, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) reaffirms its commitment to environmental conservation, embodying the global Toyota Environmental Challenge 2050 (TEC 2050) consisting of six visionary challenges ‘Going Beyond Zero Environmental Impact and Achieving Net Positive Impact’, which includes minimising and optimising water usage as well Establishing a Future Society in Harmony with Nature.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/mar-20/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-reaffirms-its-commitment-to-environmental-stewardship-and-sustainable-practices-on-the-world-forest-day-and-world-water-day-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>March 18 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Successfully Concludes Women’s Day Celebrations Strengthening Commitment to Women Empowerment and Inclusivity</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 18th March 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to empowering women and enhancing their representation within the automotive industry, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) recently concluded two vibrant events commemorating International Women's Day 2025. The celebrations, conducted on March 12 and March 16 at TKM’s manufacturing facility in Bidadi, witnessed enthusiastic participation from over 700 women employees, demonstrating the company's dedication towards creating an inclusive and inspiring work environment.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/mar-18/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-successfully-concludes-womens-day-celebrations-strengthening-commitment-to-women-empowerment-and-inclusivity.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>March 07 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Introduces Hilux Black Edition - The Ultimate Blend of Boldness, Power and Sophistication </title>
    <summary>Bengaluru, 07th March 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the Introduction of the new Hilux Black Edition in India, to cater to the desires of the customers seeking an incredible lifestyle utility vehicle that is best suited for off-roading adventure drives on tough terrains and everyday city use. Designed to keep up with evolving customer expectations, the new Hilux Black Edition aims to deliver aggressive and sophisticated all-black theme, while retaining its legendary toughness, power and performance.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/mar-07/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-introduces-hilux-black-edition.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>March 06 2025</date>
    <title>     Toyota Kirloskar Motor Commemorates International Women’s Day 2025 with a Strong Commitment to Gender Diversity and Inclusion</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 06th March 2025:  In celebration of International Women’s Day, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) reaffirms its commitment to fostering gender diversity and empowering women in the automotive industry. As part of its ongoing efforts to break gender barriers in the industry, TKM continues to prioritize policies and infrastructure that support women across manufacturing, technical, and leadership roles. With an aim to achieve 30% female representation by 2030, TKM has implemented a range of initiatives to support and uplift women within the organization. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/mar-06/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-commemorates-international-womens-day-2025-with-a-strong-commitment-to-gender-diversity-and-inclusion.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>March 05 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Introduces Legender 4X4 in All New Manual Transmission (MT) Grade</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 05th March 2025: Addressing the growing demand for high-performance, adventurous and stylish SUVs, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today introduced the Manual Transmission (MT) variant of the Toyota Legender 4X4. Designed for thrill seeking driving enthusiasts, this new variant enhances engagement and control while delivering a perfect blend of power, luxury, and cutting-edge technology.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/mar-05/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-introduces-legender-4x4-in-all-new-manual-transmission-mt-grade.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>March 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Drives 13% Growth in February 2025 </title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 01st March 2025:  Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has announced sales of 28,414 units in the month of February 2025 signifying an increase of 13% as compared to the same period last year thus reinforcing a strong market acceptance and customer trust. Building on its momentum, the growth in sales represents a significant increase compared to the 25,220 units sold in February 2024, further solidifying Toyota’s growing commitment to delivering unparalleled quality and a superior ownership experience across all touchpoints. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-drives-growth-in-february-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 27 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Advances Community Well-Being with the Inauguration of Water Units in Mysore District</title>
    <summary>Mysore, 27th February 2025: In line with its ongoing commitment to community well-being and giving it back to the society, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the inauguration of water purification units in Mysore district. The event was marked by the presence of esteemed dignitaries including Dr. Yathindra Siddaramaiah, Member, Karnataka Vidhana Parishath along with senior TKM leadership Mr. Sudeep Dalvi, Chief Communication Officer, Senior Vice President &amp; Head State Affairs - Toyota Kirloskar Motor, acknowledging the transformative impact of this initiative. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-27/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-advances-community-well-being-with-the-inauguration-of-water-units-in-mysore-district.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 25 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Honoured with ‘Star Performer Award’ at the Prestigious EEPC India National Export Awards </title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 25th February 2025: Recognising its export excellence, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) was recently honoured with the ‘Star Performer Award’ at the 54th EEPC India National Export Awards held at New Delhi. The award was presented for the company’s exemplary export performance under the engineering products, specifically in the category of Engines &amp; Parts under the Large Enterprise segment for the export year 2021-22.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-25/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-honoured-with-star-performer-award-at-the-prestigious-eepc-india-national-export-awards.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 19 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Opens Bookings for the Land Cruiser 300 - A Pinnacle of Power, Luxury, and Off-Road Dominance</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 19th February 2025– Toyota Kirloskar Motor today announced the commencement of bookings of the Land Cruiser 300, an icon of prestige, power, and rugged capability. Built upon a legacy of over 70 years, the Land Cruiser 300 is the ultimate expression of Toyota’s engineering excellence, designed to meet the expectations of luxury seekers and off-road enthusiasts.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-19/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-opens-bookings-for-the-land-cruiser-300-a-pinnacle-of-power-luxury-and-off-road-dominance.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 17 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Reinforces Commitment to Road Safety, Launches Road Safety Awareness &amp; Health Initiative for 1,250+ Drivers in Mizoram</title>
    <summary>Mizoram, 17th February 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to promote safe driving practices, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the launch of awareness and health check-up initiative for over 1,250 drivers in Mizoram. Coinciding with ‘Road Safety Month’ (January 18 – February 17, 2025), the initiative is in response to rising road accidents across the state. The occasion was graced by the distinguished presence of the chief guest Mr. Stephen Lalrinawma MPS, Senior Superintendent of Police, Traffic, Aizawl, Mr. Zorammawia Tochhawng, Dealer Principal, Zote Toyota and executives from TKM.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-17/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-reinforces-commitment-to-road-safety-launches-road-safety-awareness-health-initiative-for-1250-drivers-in-mizoram.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 14 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Inspires Young Innovators with 24-Hour Toyota Hackathon 2025 in Bangalore</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 14th February 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to fostering innovation in road safety and celebrating ‘Road Safety Month’ (January 18 – February 17, 2025), Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the successful completion of the 24-Hour Toyota Hackathon 2025 at R V Institute of Technology &amp; Management, JP Nagar, Bangalore. This event marked the third and final chapter of TKM’s hackathon series for the year, following its successful editions in Delhi and Mumbai.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-14/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-inspires-young-innovators-with-24-hour-toyota-hackathon-2025-in-bangalore.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 13 2025</date>
    <title>Government of Karnataka Honours Late Mr. Vikram S. Kirloskar with ‘Industrial Legacy’ Award for His Visionary Leadership and Pioneering Contributions to Industrial Growth at Invest Karnataka 2025 Global Investors Meet</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 13th February 2025: The Government of Karnataka has posthumously honoured Late Mr. Vikram S. Kirloskar, former Vice Chairman of Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) with the ‘Industrial Legacy’ Award for his visionary leadership, pioneering contributions, and transformative role in shaping Karnataka’s industrial, economic, and social landscape. The felicitation, presented at the Invest Karnataka 2025 Global Investors Meet (GIM), acknowledges his lifelong commitment to industrialization, job creation, skill development, and strengthening local supplier ecosystem all of which have significantly contributed to Karnataka’s emergence as a global manufacturing hub. Further solidifying his legacy, Toyota Kirloskar Motor was also honoured with the ‘Sunrise Sector Pioneer Award’ in the Automotive Division at the event, recognizing the company’s leadership in innovation, sustainability, and economic growth in Karnataka—a testament to the strong foundation laid by Late Mr. Vikram S. Kirloskar.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-13/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/government-of-karnataka-honours-late-mr-vikram-s-kirloskar-with-industrial-legacy-award-for-his-visionary.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 12 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Champions Hygiene Awareness with Annual District-Level Quiz and Drawing Competition in Raichur</title>
    <summary>Raichur, 12th February 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to promoting health, hygiene, and sanitation awareness among young minds, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the successful culmination of the Annual District-Level Quiz and Drawing Competition under ABCD (A Behavioural Change Demonstration) program, held at Raita Bhavana, Raichur. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-12/thumb-dlq-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-champions-hygiene-awareness-with-annual-district-level-quiz-and-drawing-competition-in-raichur.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 12 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Reaffirms Commitment to Karnataka’s Growth and Sustainable Future at Invest Karnataka 2025 Global Investors Meet</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 12th February 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) proudly reaffirms its commitment to Karnataka’s sustainable growth and inclusive development through its participation in the Invest Karnataka 2025 Global Investors Meet (GIM), being held from February 11th to 14th, 2025, at Bangalore Palace, Bengaluru. Under the theme ‘Reimagining Growth’, GIM 2025 serves as a global platform uniting industry pioneers, policymakers, and investors to explore transformative opportunities in sustainability, innovation, and industrial progress. With a rich history in Karnataka spanning over 25 years, TKM remains deeply committed to supporting the state’s aspirations for economic growth, job creation, and green mobility.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-12/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-reaffirms-commitment-to-karnatakas-growth-and-sustainable-future-at-invest-karnataka-2025-global-investors-meet.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 11 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Reinforces its Commitment to Sustainable Mobility at India Energy Week 2025</title>
    <summary>New Delhi, 11th February 2025 – Reiterating its commitment to India’s vision for Energy Independence by 2047 and Net Zero by 2070, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today marked its participation at the India Energy Week 2025, being held in Delhi during 11th – 14th Feb 2025. The India Energy Week 2025 (IEW) serves as an important platform to showcase practical and scalable clean energy solutions to realize energy self-reliance and reduce carbon emissions. This event brings together global political leaders, policy makers, thought leaders, experts, and end-users to deliberate on energy scenario, technologies, industry trends and policy outlook. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-11/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-reinforces-its-commitment-to-sustainable-mobility-at-india-energy-week-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 10 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Empowers Future Road Safety Leaders Through TSEP in Mumbai</title>
    <summary>Mumbai, 10th February 2025: Reinforcing its unwavering commitment to road safety, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) successfully concluded its Annual Toyota Safety Education Programme (TSEP) event in Mumbai. Held at the prestigious Sophia Bhabha Auditorium, Sophia College campus, the event marked the culmination of TSEP's annual activities in 2025 across Bengaluru, Delhi, and Mumbai. Themed "Road Safety – My Right, My Responsibility," the program aims to foster responsible road usage among future generations by engaging school children as proactive safety ambassadors.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-10/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-empowers-future-road-safety-leaders-through-tsep-in-mumbai.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 08 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Concludes Annual Toyota Safety Education Programme- Batch 2, in Bangalore, Reinforcing Commitment to Road Safety Awareness</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 08th February 2025: Staying true to its unwavering commitment to road safety, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) successfully concluded the second annual edition of its flagship Toyota Safety Education Programme (TSEP) in Bangalore. The program, aptly titled “Road Safety – My Right, My Responsibility,” continues to empower future road users with the knowledge and responsibility necessary for safer roads across India.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-08/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-concludes-annual-toyota-safety-education-programme--batch-2-in-bangalore-reinforcing-commitment-to-road-safety-awareness.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 07 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Expands Road Safety Commitment with Successful Conclusion of Toyota Safety Education Programme in Delhi</title>
    <summary>Delhi, 7th February 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to road safety, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today successfully concluded its flagship initiative, the Toyota Safety Education Programme (TSEP) – "Road Safety – My Right, My Responsibility"— at KV No. 2 Cantonment, Dr. Sarvapalli Auditorium, Delhi. This impactful event was graced by Chief Guest Mr. Rajnesh Singh – Director, Ministry of Heavy Industries alongside esteemed Guest of Honour Mr. S.K. Singh, Deputy Commissioner of Police (Traffic) and TKM's senior leadership, including Mr. Vikram Gulati, Country Head and Executive Vice President - Corporate Affairs and Governance, Toyota Kirloskar Motor.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/feb-07/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-expands-road-safety-commitment-with-successful-conclusion-of-toyota-safety-education-programme-in-delhi.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>February 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Continues to Register Growth in 2025 </title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 01st February 2025:  Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has registered a double-digit growth of 19% with sales of 29,371 units in the month of January 2025, as compared to 24,609 units sold in January 2024. Riding on its exceptional sales performance from 2024, the continued momentum underscores TKM’s sharp focus on customer centricity, enhancing customer access across the country and increasing emphasis on innovative value-added solutions.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-continues-to-register-growth-in-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 30 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Signs MoU with Watershed Organisation Trust for the Launch of ‘Project Jeevan Dhara’ for Watershed Development in Aurad Taluk, Karnataka</title>
    <summary>Bidar, 30th January 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has reaffirmed its commitment to sustainable development and community upliftment by signing a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Watershed Organisation Trust (WOTR) to implement Project Jeevan Dhara, an initiative to transform rural lives though integrated watershed management. This marks TKM's first such initiative, aiming to revitalize the drought-prone Aurad Taluk in Bidar District, Karnataka, by addressing critical socio-economic and environmental challenges.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-30/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-signs-mou-with-watershed-organisation-trust-launch-project-jeevan-dhara-watershed-development-aurad-taluk-karnataka.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 29 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Concludes 24-Hour Toyota Hackathon 2025 in Mumbai, Empowering Young Innovators to Drive Road Safety Solutions</title>
    <summary>Mumbai, 29th January 2025: Reaffirming its commitment to education and road safety, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the successful culmination of its 24-hour Toyota Hackathon 2025 held at Vidyalankar Institute, Wadala (East), Mumbai. Coinciding with ‘Road Safety Month’ (January 18 – February 17, 2025), the event brought together over 400 talented students from 100+ schools across Mumbai, providing a platform to develop actionable solutions to critical road safety challenges.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-29/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-concludes-24-hour-toyota-hackathon-2025-in-mumbai-empowering-young-innovators-to-drive-road-safety-solutions.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 28 2025</date>
    <title>Varanasi Selects 10 Semi-Finalists for Global $3 Million Mobility Challenge To Reimagine Crowd Management</title>
    <summary>VARANASI, 28th January 2025 India: The Toyota Mobility Foundation has announced its ten semi-finalists for its  in Varanasi’s old city, Kashi. Developed in partnership with the , , and , the Challenge sought global innovators to create scalable, data-driven solutions to reimagine crowd management in the city. Varanasi, one of India’s most iconic heritage and spiritual cities, draws a substantial number of tourists. This influx also presented an opportunity to develop innovative, data-driven solutions aimed at improving the city’s safety and accessibility, benefiting religious tourists, residents, and vulnerable communities alike.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/varanasi-selects-10-semi-finalists-for-global-$3-million-mobility-challenge-to-reimagine-crowd-management.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 25 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Signs MoU with B.L.D.E.A's V.P. Dr.P.G.Halakatti College of Engineering and Technology, Vijayapura to Establish its 26th Centre of Excellence for Skill Development</title>
    <summary>Vijayapura, 25th January 2025: As part of its continuous efforts to bridge the gap between industry and academia, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with B.L.D.E.A's V.P. Dr.P.G.Halakatti College of Engineering and Technology to establish a Centre of Excellence (CoE) on campus. This initiative aims to equip students with practical knowledge and technical expertise in engines, powertrains, and their functionalities. By aligning academic learning with real-world industry demands, TKM aims to foster innovation, drive skill development, and prepare a future-ready workforce capable of addressing the evolving needs of the automotive sector.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-25/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-signs-mou-with-bldeas-vp-drpghalakatti-college-of-engineering-and-technology-vijayapura-to-establish-its-26th-centre-of-excellence-for-skill-development.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 25 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Breaks Ground for Educational Infrastructure Development in Vijayapura </title>
    <summary>Mamadapura, 25th January 2025: In a significant step towards fostering educational empowerment in rural Karnataka, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today marked a significant milestone with the successful ground-breaking ceremony for its comprehensive educational infrastructure development project in Vijayapura. The prestigious event was graced by the Hon’ble Minister for Industries, Government of Karnataka, Dr. M. B. Patil, alongside senior leaders from TKM, Mr. Sudeep Dalvi, Chief Communication Officer, Senior Vice President &amp; Head State Affairs, and Mr. Roshan, General Manager.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-25/thumb-1-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-breaks-ground-for-educational-infrastructure-development-in-vijayapura.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 23 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Concludes 24-Hour Hackathon in Delhi, Celebrating Road Safety Month 2025, Empowering Young Innovators </title>
    <summary>Delhi, 23rd January 2025: As part of its ongoing commitment to fostering road safety innovation and celebrating ‘Road Safety Month’ (January 18 – February 17, 2025), Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) proudly announced the successful conclusion of the 24-hour Toyota Hackathon at GL Bajaj Institute, Greater Noida, Delhi. The event, graced by Chief Guest Mr Ashok Kumar IPS , Additional Deputy Commissioner of Police, Greater Noida UP, Guest of Honour Mr RR Meena Deputy Secretary, Ministry of Road Transport and Highways, Government of India  and TKM’s senior leadership, including Mr. Vikram Gulati, Country Head &amp; Executive Vice President, Corporate Affairs and Governance, provided an engaging platform for young innovators to develop practical and implementable solutions to critical road safety challenges.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-23/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-concludes-24-hour-hackathon-in-delhi-celebrating-road-safety-month-2025-empowering-young-innovators.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 21 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Celebrates Excellence in Health with Annual District-Level Quiz and Drawing Competition</title>
    <summary>Raichur, 21th January 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the successful culmination of the Annual District-Level Quiz and Drawing Competition under ABCD (A Behavioural Change Demonstration) program, held at Krishi Vignana Kendra, Raichur. This event marked a significant milestone in TKM's ongoing commitment to fostering sustainable health, hygiene, and sanitation practices among school children in the region. The event was graced by Mr. K.D Badiger, Deputy Director of School Education (DDPI) - Admin, Raichur and Mr. Soppa Eswar Babu, Manager at TKM, whose presence further underscored the significance of this initiative.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-21/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-celebrates-excellence-in-health-with-annual-district-level-quiz-and-drawing-competition.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 20 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Concludes 33rd iCARE Event with a Focus on STEM Education</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 20th January 2025: Reinforcing its commitment to holistic community development, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the culmination of its 33rd iCARE (i, Community Action to Reach Everyone) activity on 19th January, at Government High School, Doddagholarahatti, near Kengeri. This impactful initiative saw the participation of 200 enthusiastic iCARE volunteers, along with 100 students from the host school, working collaboratively to design and build interactive STEM models such as hand pumps, solar energy systems, geo boards, and electromagnets. This effort, aligning with International Education Month, underscores Toyota’s dedication to nurturing young minds through experiential learning, promoting a 'learn by doing' approach that is crucial to foster problem-solving skills and creative thinking. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-20/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-concludes-33rd-icare-event-with-a-focus-on-stem-education.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 19 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Showcases Comprehensive Mobility Solutions at Bharat Mobility Global Expo 2025</title>
    <summary>New Delhi, 19th January 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) further added to the excitement at the Bharat Mobility Global Expo 2025 by showcasing an extensive range of specialized vehicles and innovative mobility solutions at its Toyota Mobility Service (TMS) stall. Built on the legendary Toyota Hilux platform, these vehicles highlight Toyota’s enduring commitment to advancing industrial mobility, operational efficiency, and sustainability across diverse sectors.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-19/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-showcases-comprehensive-mobility-solutions-at-bharat-mobility-global-expo-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 18 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Concludes the Second Year of Annual Toyota Safety Education Programme in Bangalore, and Continues to Drive Road Safety Awareness across India</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 18th January 2025: In a dedicated effort to enhance road safety awareness, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has been steadfastly working towards creating safer roads through its flagship initiative, the Toyota Safety Education Programme (TSEP) – "Road Safety – My Right, My Responsibility." Continuing this commitment, TKM announced the successful culmination of the second year of its inaugural batch at the Annual TSEP event, held for the second consecutive year in Bangalore.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-18/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-concludes-the-second-year-of-annual-toyota-safety-education-programme-in-bangalore.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 17 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Brings the Spirit of ‘Happier Paths Together’ to Bharat Mobility Global Expo 2025</title>
    <summary>New Delhi, 17th January 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has showcased its exciting range of products and advanced technologies at Auto Expo - The Motor Show, Bharat Mobility Global Expo 2025, designed to meet the evolving needs and aspirations of the customers, while delivering on its promise of ‘Mass Happiness for All’. In pursuit of achieving carbon neutrality through a multi-pathway approach, the Toyota pavilion demonstrates its holistic strategy in India under the banner of “Happier Path Together” a vision that aligns with the company’s global commitment to sustainable growth and societal wellbeing. </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-17/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-brings-the-spirit-of-happier-paths-together-to-bharat-mobility-global-expo-2025.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 15 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Launches Toyota Mobility Solutions and Services to Redefine Pre-Owned Car Market in India</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, India – January 15, 2025 – Emphasizing its focus on becoming a true mobility company with a commitment to delivering ever-better cars, Toyota Kirloskar Motor today announced the launch of its wholly owned subsidiary, Toyota Mobility Solutions and Services India Pvt. Ltd. (TMSS) with Head Office in Bidadi near Bangalore in Karnataka. Marking a significant stride towards transforming India’s pre-owned car market, TMSS further reinforces Toyota’s commitment towards the philosophy of —Quality, Durability, and Reliability which ensures the best quality products and services heritage to all customers be in new car sales or pre-owned car market.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-15/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-launches-toyota-mobility-solutions-and-services-to-redefine-pre-owned-car-market-in-india.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 14 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor in association with Government of Mizoram and Zote Toyota Establishes its 67th Toyota Technical Education Program [T-TEP] and STAR Scholarship Initiative in Mizoram</title>
    <summary>Aizwal, 14th January 2024: Continuing its commitment to the nation’s ‘Skill India’ and ‘Make in India’ missions, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the launch of its 67th Toyota Technical Education Program (T-TEP) and the “Scholarship program for Technical Education and Recognition” [STAR] initiative under T-TEP at Government Industrial Training Institute (ITI), Aizwal, Mizoram.  Reaffirming TKM’s unwavering commitment to fostering skill development and enhancing employability opportunities across the area. The initiative is a collaboration between TKM, the Government of Mizoram, and dealership partner Zote Toyota, underscoring their shared commitment to enhancing youth employability and fostering skill development. The launch event was graced by Chief Guest Mr. Lalnghinglova Hmar, Minister of State - Labour, Employment, Skill Development &amp; Entrepreneurship Dept. Government of Mizoram</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-14/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-in-association-with-government-of-mizoram-and-zote-toyota-establishes-its-67th-toyota-technical-education-program.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 10 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Signs MoU with Government Tool Room &amp; Training Centre to Enhance Skill Development in Karnataka</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 10th January 2025: Reinforcing its dedication to skill development and community empowerment, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Government Tool Room &amp; Training Centre (GTTC), Karnataka. The MoU, effective from January 2025, underscores TKM’s role in elevating the quality of training at GTTC centers and Multi-Skill Development Centres (MSDCs) by introducing advanced industry culture, faculty development programs, and modern training materials. By bridging the gap between academia and industry, the initiative underscores TKM's commitment to empowering trainees with the skills needed to excel in today’s competitive industrial landscape.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-10/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-signs-mou-with-government-tool-room-training-centre-to-enhance-skill-development-in-karnataka.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 07 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Announces the 18th Edition of the “Toyota Dream Car Art Contest”</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 07th January 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM)is delighted to present the 18th Toyota Dream Car Art Contest (TDCAC), an annual contest that invites young artists to unleash their creativity and reimagine the future of mobility on a unique and inspiring platform.  The contest that invites children to reimagine the future of mobility by drawing their dream cars is open to children across India from January 6 to January 31, 2025, </summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-07/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-announces-the-18th-edition-of-the-toyota-dream-car-art-contest.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 03 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Scales Up Anganwadi Development Program to Benefit 400 New Centers in Ramanagara District</title>
    <summary>Ramanagara, 03rd January 2025: Demonstrating its unwavering commitment to community development, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM), in collaboration with the Government of Karnataka, is proud to announce the expansion of its flagship Toyota Anganwadi Development Program (TADP). Building on the success of the initial phase that developed 30 model Anganwadi Centres (AWCs), the program was scaled up to 150 centers in FY 2023-24. Recognizing its impact, the initiative is now being extended to an additional 400 AWCs in Ramanagara district from December 2024 to March 2026.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/jan-03/thumb-311x175.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-scales-up-anganwadi-development-program-to-benefit-400-new-centers-in-ramanagara-district.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>January 01 2025</date>
    <title>Toyota Kirloskar Motor Records Its Highest Ever Calendar Year Sales in 2024 by Selling 3,26,329 Units</title>
    <summary>Bangalore, 01st January 2025: Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) marked a significant milestone in 2024 by recording its best-ever calendar year sales, achieving a sale of 3,26,329 units thus reflecting an impressive 40% growth over the 2,33,346 units sold in 2023. This achievement underscores TKM’s unwavering commitment towards delivering high-quality vehicles suited to meet the market’s diverse needs thus leading to a growing market presence.</summary>
    <image>/images/news/2025/thumb-toyota.jpg</image>
    <url>/news/2025/tkm-records-its-highest-ever-calendar-year-sales-in-2024-by-selling-326329-units.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>18th November 2025</date>
    <title>&lt;![CDATA[Untitled]]&gt;</title>
    <summary>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mangalagiri, 18th November 2025: &lt;/strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the handover of essential classroom infrastructure and learning support materials to rural schools in Andhra Pradesh, under its Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) program for FY 2025-26. As part of this initiative, TKM extended support to 13 government schools in Mangalagiri taluk of Guntur district, benefiting more than 3,600 students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Piloting this initiative in Andhra Pradesh, TKM is working to enhance learning environments in government schools. The intervention focuses on upgrading classroom infrastructure, supporting hygienic preparation of mid-day meals, and creating spaces that encourage active participation in sports activities. The effort aims to make schools more engaging, inclusive, and conducive to growth. Early outcomes include improved classroom spaces with better quality furniture that improves the overall learning experience, hygienic meal preparation that enhances nutritional value, and increased student participation in sports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A formal handover ceremony took place at the District Collector’s office, in the presence of Ms.  A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector (DC), Ms. C V Renuka, District Education Officer (DEO), and members of TKM’s CSR Division. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Appreciating TKM’s efforts,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Ms. A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector,&lt;em&gt; said,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “We appreciate TKM’s efforts in strengthening educational infrastructure in Guntur district. The support provided to these schools will enhance both learning and extracurricular opportunities for our students. We are confident that this intervention will have a positive impact on the educational outcomes and the holistic development of children in our communities.” &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaking on the initiative, Mr. Vikram Gulati, Country Head and Executive Vice President, Corporate Affairs and Governance, Toyota Kirloskar Motor, said,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “True transformation begins at the grassroots level. Education has the power to uplift individuals and strengthen entire communities. At TKM, we believe quality education goes beyond conventional learning. It includes creative opportunities, engaging learning spaces, supportive environments, and attention to students’ overall well-being. Our efforts focus on creating inspiring spaces where children can learn, grow, and dream freely. By strengthening schools and supporting students’ well-being, we hope to build strong foundations that empower every child to shape a brighter future.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since 2001, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has been committed to uplifting communities across Education, Environment, Road Safety, Skill Development, Health &amp;amp; Hygiene, and Disaster Management. At TKM, CSR reflects a deep commitment to encouraging meaningful socio-economic development through need-based initiatives. Guided by its “Child to Community” approach, TKM focuses on holistic interventions that create long-term impact, going beyond its expectations to support education, infrastructure, and overall well-being. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By investing in the education and well-being of children, TKM contributes to the long-term vision of a developed, inclusive, and empowered India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of TKM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equity participation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Motor Corporation (Japan) : 89%, Kirloskar Systems Limited (India) : 11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of employees&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 6,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Land area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 432 acres (approx.1,700,000 m2)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;74,000 m2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Total Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 3,42,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 1st Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Established&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;October 1997 (start of production: December 1999)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innova HyCross, Innova Crysta , Fortuner, Legender manufactured in India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 1,32,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 2nd Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start of Production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;December 2010&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the site of Toyota Kirloskar Motor Private Limited, Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Camry Hybrid, Urban Cruiser Hyryder, Hilux&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 2,10,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Other Toyota Models: Glanza, Rumion, Urban Cruiser Taisor &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; **Imported as CBU: Vellfire, LC 300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Any Further Queries, Please Contact:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Pvt. Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swathi Rajagopal&lt;br /&gt;  Email: &lt;a href="mailto:swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in"&gt;swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis Value 360&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anusha Banerjee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  Email: anusha@lewisvalue360.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;]]&gt;</summary>
    <image>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img class="img-responsive" src="D:/practise-projects/tb/press-relese-automation/data/images/news/2025/nov-18/press-release-main-01-800x514.jpg" alt="Untitled" title="Untitled"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Untitled&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;br&gt;</image>
    <url>D:\practise-projects\tb\press-relese-automation\output\html/untitled.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>18th November 2025</date>
    <title>&lt;![CDATA[Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh]]&gt;</title>
    <summary>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mangalagiri, 18th November 2025: &lt;/strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the handover of essential classroom infrastructure and learning support materials to rural schools in Andhra Pradesh, under its Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) program for FY 2025-26. As part of this initiative, TKM extended support to 13 government schools in Mangalagiri taluk of Guntur district, benefiting more than 3,600 students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Piloting this initiative in Andhra Pradesh, TKM is working to enhance learning environments in government schools. The intervention focuses on upgrading classroom infrastructure, supporting hygienic preparation of mid-day meals, and creating spaces that encourage active participation in sports activities. The effort aims to make schools more engaging, inclusive, and conducive to growth. Early outcomes include improved classroom spaces with better quality furniture that improves the overall learning experience, hygienic meal preparation that enhances nutritional value, and increased student participation in sports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A formal handover ceremony took place at the District Collector’s office, in the presence of Ms.  A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector (DC), Ms. C V Renuka, District Education Officer (DEO), and members of TKM’s CSR Division. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Appreciating TKM’s efforts,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Ms. A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector,&lt;em&gt; said,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “We appreciate TKM’s efforts in strengthening educational infrastructure in Guntur district. The support provided to these schools will enhance both learning and extracurricular opportunities for our students. We are confident that this intervention will have a positive impact on the educational outcomes and the holistic development of children in our communities.” &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaking on the initiative, Mr. Vikram Gulati, Country Head and Executive Vice President, Corporate Affairs and Governance, Toyota Kirloskar Motor, said,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “True transformation begins at the grassroots level. Education has the power to uplift individuals and strengthen entire communities. At TKM, we believe quality education goes beyond conventional learning. It includes creative opportunities, engaging learning spaces, supportive environments, and attention to students’ overall well-being. Our efforts focus on creating inspiring spaces where children can learn, grow, and dream freely. By strengthening schools and supporting students’ well-being, we hope to build strong foundations that empower every child to shape a brighter future.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since 2001, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has been committed to uplifting communities across Education, Environment, Road Safety, Skill Development, Health &amp;amp; Hygiene, and Disaster Management. At TKM, CSR reflects a deep commitment to encouraging meaningful socio-economic development through need-based initiatives. Guided by its “Child to Community” approach, TKM focuses on holistic interventions that create long-term impact, going beyond its expectations to support education, infrastructure, and overall well-being. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By investing in the education and well-being of children, TKM contributes to the long-term vision of a developed, inclusive, and empowered India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of TKM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equity participation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Motor Corporation (Japan) : 89%, Kirloskar Systems Limited (India) : 11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of employees&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 6,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Land area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 432 acres (approx.1,700,000 m2)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;74,000 m2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Total Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 3,42,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 1st Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Established&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;October 1997 (start of production: December 1999)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innova HyCross, Innova Crysta , Fortuner, Legender manufactured in India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 1,32,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 2nd Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start of Production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;December 2010&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the site of Toyota Kirloskar Motor Private Limited, Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Camry Hybrid, Urban Cruiser Hyryder, Hilux&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 2,10,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Other Toyota Models: Glanza, Rumion, Urban Cruiser Taisor &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; **Imported as CBU: Vellfire, LC 300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Any Further Queries, Please Contact:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Pvt. Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swathi Rajagopal&lt;br /&gt;  Email: &lt;a href="mailto:swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in"&gt;swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis Value 360&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anusha Banerjee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  Email: anusha@lewisvalue360.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;]]&gt;</summary>
    <image>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img class="img-responsive" src="D:/practise-projects/tb/press-relese-automation/data/images/news/2025/nov-18/press-release-main-01-800x514.jpg" alt="Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh" title="Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;br&gt;</image>
    <url>D:\practise-projects\tb\press-relese-automation\output\html/tkm-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>18th November 2025</date>
    <title>&lt;![CDATA[Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh]]&gt;</title>
    <summary>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mangalagiri, 18th November 2025: &lt;/strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the handover of essential classroom infrastructure and learning support materials to rural schools in Andhra Pradesh, under its Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) program for FY 2025-26. As part of this initiative, TKM extended support to 13 government schools in Mangalagiri taluk of Guntur district, benefiting more than 3,600 students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Piloting this initiative in Andhra Pradesh, TKM is working to enhance learning environments in government schools. The intervention focuses on upgrading classroom infrastructure, supporting hygienic preparation of mid-day meals, and creating spaces that encourage active participation in sports activities. The effort aims to make schools more engaging, inclusive, and conducive to growth. Early outcomes include improved classroom spaces with better quality furniture that improves the overall learning experience, hygienic meal preparation that enhances nutritional value, and increased student participation in sports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A formal handover ceremony took place at the District Collector’s office, in the presence of Ms.  A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector (DC), Ms. C V Renuka, District Education Officer (DEO), and members of TKM’s CSR Division. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Appreciating TKM’s efforts,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Ms. A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector,&lt;em&gt; said,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “We appreciate TKM’s efforts in strengthening educational infrastructure in Guntur district. The support provided to these schools will enhance both learning and extracurricular opportunities for our students. We are confident that this intervention will have a positive impact on the educational outcomes and the holistic development of children in our communities.” &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaking on the initiative, Mr. Vikram Gulati, Country Head and Executive Vice President, Corporate Affairs and Governance, Toyota Kirloskar Motor, said,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “True transformation begins at the grassroots level. Education has the power to uplift individuals and strengthen entire communities. At TKM, we believe quality education goes beyond conventional learning. It includes creative opportunities, engaging learning spaces, supportive environments, and attention to students’ overall well-being. Our efforts focus on creating inspiring spaces where children can learn, grow, and dream freely. By strengthening schools and supporting students’ well-being, we hope to build strong foundations that empower every child to shape a brighter future.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since 2001, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has been committed to uplifting communities across Education, Environment, Road Safety, Skill Development, Health &amp;amp; Hygiene, and Disaster Management. At TKM, CSR reflects a deep commitment to encouraging meaningful socio-economic development through need-based initiatives. Guided by its “Child to Community” approach, TKM focuses on holistic interventions that create long-term impact, going beyond its expectations to support education, infrastructure, and overall well-being. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By investing in the education and well-being of children, TKM contributes to the long-term vision of a developed, inclusive, and empowered India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of TKM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equity participation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Motor Corporation (Japan) : 89%, Kirloskar Systems Limited (India) : 11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of employees&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 6,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Land area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 432 acres (approx.1,700,000 m2)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;74,000 m2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Total Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 3,42,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 1st Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Established&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;October 1997 (start of production: December 1999)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innova HyCross, Innova Crysta , Fortuner, Legender manufactured in India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 1,32,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 2nd Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start of Production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;December 2010&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the site of Toyota Kirloskar Motor Private Limited, Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Camry Hybrid, Urban Cruiser Hyryder, Hilux&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 2,10,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Other Toyota Models: Glanza, Rumion, Urban Cruiser Taisor &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; **Imported as CBU: Vellfire, LC 300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Any Further Queries, Please Contact:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Pvt. Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swathi Rajagopal&lt;br /&gt;  Email: &lt;a href="mailto:swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in"&gt;swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis Value 360&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anusha Banerjee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  Email: anusha@lewisvalue360.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;]]&gt;</summary>
    <image>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img class="img-responsive" src="D:/practise-projects/tb/press-relese-automation/data/images/news/2025/nov-18/press-release-main-01-800x514.jpg" alt="Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh" title="Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;br&gt;</image>
    <url>D:\practise-projects\tb\press-relese-automation\output\html/tkm-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>18th November 2025</date>
    <title>&lt;![CDATA[Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh]]&gt;</title>
    <summary>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mangalagiri, 18th November 2025: &lt;/strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the handover of essential classroom infrastructure and learning support materials to rural schools in Andhra Pradesh, under its Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) program for FY 2025-26. As part of this initiative, TKM extended support to 13 government schools in Mangalagiri taluk of Guntur district, benefiting more than 3,600 students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Piloting this initiative in Andhra Pradesh, TKM is working to enhance learning environments in government schools. The intervention focuses on upgrading classroom infrastructure, supporting hygienic preparation of mid-day meals, and creating spaces that encourage active participation in sports activities. The effort aims to make schools more engaging, inclusive, and conducive to growth. Early outcomes include improved classroom spaces with better quality furniture that improves the overall learning experience, hygienic meal preparation that enhances nutritional value, and increased student participation in sports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A formal handover ceremony took place at the District Collector’s office, in the presence of Ms.  A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector (DC), Ms. C V Renuka, District Education Officer (DEO), and members of TKM’s CSR Division. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Appreciating TKM’s efforts,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Ms. A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector,&lt;em&gt; said,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “We appreciate TKM’s efforts in strengthening educational infrastructure in Guntur district. The support provided to these schools will enhance both learning and extracurricular opportunities for our students. We are confident that this intervention will have a positive impact on the educational outcomes and the holistic development of children in our communities.” &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaking on the initiative, Mr. Vikram Gulati, Country Head and Executive Vice President, Corporate Affairs and Governance, Toyota Kirloskar Motor, said,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “True transformation begins at the grassroots level. Education has the power to uplift individuals and strengthen entire communities. At TKM, we believe quality education goes beyond conventional learning. It includes creative opportunities, engaging learning spaces, supportive environments, and attention to students’ overall well-being. Our efforts focus on creating inspiring spaces where children can learn, grow, and dream freely. By strengthening schools and supporting students’ well-being, we hope to build strong foundations that empower every child to shape a brighter future.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since 2001, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has been committed to uplifting communities across Education, Environment, Road Safety, Skill Development, Health &amp;amp; Hygiene, and Disaster Management. At TKM, CSR reflects a deep commitment to encouraging meaningful socio-economic development through need-based initiatives. Guided by its “Child to Community” approach, TKM focuses on holistic interventions that create long-term impact, going beyond its expectations to support education, infrastructure, and overall well-being. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By investing in the education and well-being of children, TKM contributes to the long-term vision of a developed, inclusive, and empowered India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of TKM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equity participation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Motor Corporation (Japan) : 89%, Kirloskar Systems Limited (India) : 11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of employees&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 6,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Land area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 432 acres (approx.1,700,000 m2)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;74,000 m2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Total Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 3,42,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 1st Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Established&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;October 1997 (start of production: December 1999)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innova HyCross, Innova Crysta , Fortuner, Legender manufactured in India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 1,32,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 2nd Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start of Production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;December 2010&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the site of Toyota Kirloskar Motor Private Limited, Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Camry Hybrid, Urban Cruiser Hyryder, Hilux&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 2,10,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Other Toyota Models: Glanza, Rumion, Urban Cruiser Taisor &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; **Imported as CBU: Vellfire, LC 300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Any Further Queries, Please Contact:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Pvt. Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swathi Rajagopal&lt;br /&gt;  Email: &lt;a href="mailto:swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in"&gt;swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis Value 360&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anusha Banerjee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  Email: anusha@lewisvalue360.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;]]&gt;</summary>
    <image>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img class="img-responsive" src="D:/practise-projects/tb/press-relese-automation/data/images/news/2025/nov-18/press-release-main-01-800x514.jpg" alt="Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh" title="Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;br&gt;</image>
    <url>D:\practise-projects\tb\press-relese-automation\output\html/tkm-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <date>18th November 2025</date>
    <title>&lt;![CDATA[Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh]]&gt;</title>
    <summary>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More than 3,600 students from 13 government schools in Guntur district benefited.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mangalagiri, 18th November 2025: &lt;/strong&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) today announced the handover of essential classroom infrastructure and learning support materials to rural schools in Andhra Pradesh, under its Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) program for FY 2025-26. As part of this initiative, TKM extended support to 13 government schools in Mangalagiri taluk of Guntur district, benefiting more than 3,600 students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Piloting this initiative in Andhra Pradesh, TKM is working to enhance learning environments in government schools. The intervention focuses on upgrading classroom infrastructure, supporting hygienic preparation of mid-day meals, and creating spaces that encourage active participation in sports activities. The effort aims to make schools more engaging, inclusive, and conducive to growth. Early outcomes include improved classroom spaces with better quality furniture that improves the overall learning experience, hygienic meal preparation that enhances nutritional value, and increased student participation in sports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A formal handover ceremony took place at the District Collector’s office, in the presence of Ms.  A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector (DC), Ms. C V Renuka, District Education Officer (DEO), and members of TKM’s CSR Division. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Appreciating TKM’s efforts,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Ms. A. Thameem Ansariya, District Collector,&lt;em&gt; said,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “We appreciate TKM’s efforts in strengthening educational infrastructure in Guntur district. The support provided to these schools will enhance both learning and extracurricular opportunities for our students. We are confident that this intervention will have a positive impact on the educational outcomes and the holistic development of children in our communities.” &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaking on the initiative, Mr. Vikram Gulati, Country Head and Executive Vice President, Corporate Affairs and Governance, Toyota Kirloskar Motor, said,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; “True transformation begins at the grassroots level. Education has the power to uplift individuals and strengthen entire communities. At TKM, we believe quality education goes beyond conventional learning. It includes creative opportunities, engaging learning spaces, supportive environments, and attention to students’ overall well-being. Our efforts focus on creating inspiring spaces where children can learn, grow, and dream freely. By strengthening schools and supporting students’ well-being, we hope to build strong foundations that empower every child to shape a brighter future.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since 2001, Toyota Kirloskar Motor (TKM) has been committed to uplifting communities across Education, Environment, Road Safety, Skill Development, Health &amp;amp; Hygiene, and Disaster Management. At TKM, CSR reflects a deep commitment to encouraging meaningful socio-economic development through need-based initiatives. Guided by its “Child to Community” approach, TKM focuses on holistic interventions that create long-term impact, going beyond its expectations to support education, infrastructure, and overall well-being. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By investing in the education and well-being of children, TKM contributes to the long-term vision of a developed, inclusive, and empowered India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of TKM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equity participation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Motor Corporation (Japan) : 89%, Kirloskar Systems Limited (India) : 11%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of employees&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 6,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Land area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approx. 432 acres (approx.1,700,000 m2)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;74,000 m2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Total Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 3,42,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 1st Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Established&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;October 1997 (start of production: December 1999)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Innova HyCross, Innova Crysta , Fortuner, Legender manufactured in India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 1,32,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview of TKM 2nd Plant:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start of Production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;December 2010&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the site of Toyota Kirloskar Motor Private Limited, Bidadi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Camry Hybrid, Urban Cruiser Hyryder, Hilux&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installed Production capacity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to 2,10,000 units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Other Toyota Models: Glanza, Rumion, Urban Cruiser Taisor &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; **Imported as CBU: Vellfire, LC 300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Any Further Queries, Please Contact:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Pvt. Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swathi Rajagopal&lt;br /&gt;  Email: &lt;a href="mailto:swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in"&gt;swathi_rajagopal@toyota-kirloskar.co.in&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis Value 360&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anusha Banerjee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  Email: anusha@lewisvalue360.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;]]&gt;</summary>
    <image>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img class="img-responsive" src="D:/practise-projects/tb/press-relese-automation/data/images/news/2025/nov-18/press-release-main-01-800x514.jpg" alt="Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh" title="Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Toyota Kirloskar Motor Deepens CSR Impact Through Enhancement of School Education in Andhra Pradesh&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;br&gt;</image>
    <url>D:\practise-projects\tb\press-relese-automation\output\html/tkm-deepens-csr-impact-through-enhancement-of-school-education-in-andhra-pradesh.html</url>
    <category/>
  </item>
</news>